Contact

ayoinc@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ayoinc (LinkedIn) containercode.club (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Continuous Integration
Information Security
Agile & Waterfall Methodologies

Languages

Yoruba (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Serverless Architecture

Essential Cloud Infrastructure: Core Services

Docker for Java Developers

Cyber Security Fundamentals — The Open University

Networking Fundamentals - Certified 2017

Ayodele Ajayi

Site Reliability Engineer at The Rank Group Camden

Summary

A bright, talented and ambitious SRE/DevOps/SysOps / Security / Application specialist with a strong technical background who possesses self-discipline and the ability to work with the minimum of supervision. Having exposure to a wide range of technologies & able to play a key role in diagnosing hardware, software problems, analyse network logs for security and to ensure that quality solutions meet business objectives. Possessing a good team spirit, deadline orientated and having the ability to organize and present complex solutions clearly and accurately.

Experience

The Rank Group plc
Site Reliability Engineer
March 2020 - Present (9 months)

Implementing globally used processes and procedures, monitoring solutions, and building a Site Reliability. Increasing operational up-time of websites and technical services.

Adjoint Inc.

DevOps Engineer

August 2019 - March 2020 (8 months)

London, England, United Kingdom

Ops for FinTech / Smart Ledger Solution

OpenAsset

IT Engineer

January 2018 - August 2019 (1 year 8 months)

London, United Kingdom

Supporting OpenAsset Digital Asset Management Software in Cloud and OnPremise Clients

Indivior

System Analyst (IT Contractor)

Page 1 of 2

March 2016 - January 2018 (1 year 11 months)

Slough, United Kingdom

SC Johnson Senior IT Analyst August 2015 - March 2016 (8 months) Surrey, United Kingdom

New Testament Church of God Clare Valley IT Support Technician / Multimedia December 2012 - June 2015 (2 years 7 months) Romford, United Kingdom

IT Technician and Music IT.

Guardian Newspaper Nigeria IT and System Support Technician March 2011 - April 2012 (1 year 2 months) Oshodi Lagos Nigeria

Contract / Temporary Position

Education

Harvard University

Certificate, Cybersecurity: Managing Risk in the Information Age \cdot (2017 - 2018)

The Open University

Professional Development, Cyber Security for Small and Medium Businesses · (2016 - 2016)

Firebrand Academy

Professional Development, Project Management · (2016 - 2016)

Capital College UK

Diploma, Business, Management, Marketing, and Related Support Services · (2012 - 2013)

New Horizons Computer Learning Centre

Dip. Multimedia Technology, Multimedia Technology · (2012 - 2012)